Seino, rattle channel, go-go!
I was wondering if you would do it if I didn't tell you. I saw you didn't say it.
Today, I'd like to try to coordinate with GU.
Today, I'm going to look online and make a decision, but I don't think I've ever made a coordinate while looking on the Internet.
I tend to buy what I want on the Internet, and when I receive it, I put it together with what I already have,
So, I don't think I can put together my own coordination on the Internet.
Is it OK for me to make my own coordination? It's difficult.
Then, I would like to make my own coordination.
Let's put it together. It's a good opportunity.
I want you to wear something like this.
I'll go with that.
Wait a minute.
Isn't it difficult?
Well, just tell Minami you want her to wear it.
Do you want to do something more wispy or something?
Ha-ha-ha.
Wow, what a weird combination!
Ha-ha-ha, that's the worst!
But, uh...
I'll pay more than 4,000 yen for this kind of thing.
And then it's just...
That's it, that's it, that's all it's going to be
I can't cut it.
5,000 yen.
I'll give you 3,000 yen for a sticker and a price reduction.
What? We're going to make a short type of trench.
If it's a Nesari item, I'll put it together like this.
Outerwear, Dolphin?
I'll just wear spring clothes.
I'm not good at this kind of thing.
I get it.
But then again, I don't shop online much.
I know, I know.
Even if I see something on here.
I'll go see the real thing.
Oh.
990 yen.
What do you mean?
So, you know, we can put it together.
If it's this way...
Cheap!
Scary!
I don't know if I'd wear it, but... but I'm not wearing blue.
I want you to wear something colorful.
I want you to wear something colorful. - Usually I wear plain clothes.
But aren't we casual with each other?
Well, if we were to talk about taste, I'd say we're casual.
Casual, but Minami's more like a child's casual.
Casual? -Casual?
I don't know, I don't know. I don't know. But maybe Minami uses more colors.
That's right. Spunky has more colors.
Okocha Casual
Yes, so it's decided.
No, it's okay.
Did you find it OK?
Well, it was very difficult to find something.
I don't want to struggle.
There were a lot of simple designs.
There are a lot of them.
If you can add accessories...
Yes, that's right. That's why I did my best,
But I...
I might have done my shopping in 8 days.
Oh, my God.
Regardless of my body.
Yes, yes, yes.
I was thinking...well...but...
I feel like I've adopted some of the things
I feel like I've taken in some of the things that Yoka seems to be wearing.
Ha-ha-ha.
Well, I guess it's okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel like that's okay.
Yes.
Then, I'd like to buy the things I just chose.
I'd like to buy the things I just picked out.
Good morning.
I changed my clothes today.
Yes, that's right,
Minami is wearing what I'm wearing, and I'm coordinating with Kun.Minami is wearing what I'm wearing, and I'm coordinating with Kun.
Good shopping!
Yes, ma'am.
I guess this is my personal stuff. The rest are tops and bottoms.
I didn't want to put in too much color. I put in darker colors.
I don't really wear long scarp either, so I feel different. I don't wear tank tops.
You don't wear tank tops either, do you?
Yes, I don't wear sleeveless very often, so it's very fresh.
That's why I chose it.
I had such a feeling it would come.
Isn't it cute? I also made sure I chose the right shoes.
It was the first time for me to put it together online, so it was really difficult to get my imagination involved.
It was hard to put it all together in my head.
Even Minami took a lot of time.
It was difficult.
I don't really buy on the Internet.
But since there were so many simple items in the simple coordination, I had to add accessories, so I looked at the prices and did the math, and I was able to make it this far.
That's amazing.
Surprisingly, I was able to put it together for less than 5,000 yen.
That's for sure.
But I was able to wear the coords that Minami put together for me, so it was fun for me too.
Me too.
Do you want to try?
Are you going to go for the "no-three" challenge?
I'll be here this summer.
Summer is coming.
If I have a chance to wear it in the summer, I will.
I don't think I'll wear it much.
So-so, so-so.
Today's challenge.
Please wait for me.
I was thinking of trying a long skirt.
I'm tall.
I think so.
I think I have it.
So thank you for watching.
If you like this video, please give it a high rating, comment, and subscribe to my channel.
Bye bye.